



o 6 Horeya square, Maadi, Egypt



Profile

I'm a self-taught developer. Four years ago I started Front-end web development as a self-study course and learned some new technology skills. I strive to be a professional Front End web developer through teamwork and want to produce awesome real projects. I also value lifelong learning and continue to learn from e Books and video courses from top teaching resources.

Employment History

UI Developer, Road9 Media, Cairo

June 2019 — July 2020

Turn UX designs into running websites

Front End Developer, EXPAND CART, 6th of October City, Giza Governorate July 2020 — January 2022

Convert existing HTML templates to a server-side template using the twig template engine.

Fix UI bugs on current templates.

Helping formulate an effective, responsive design and turning it into a working theme.

Education

Bachelor's Degree, Faculty of Science, Suez

September 2010 — June 2014

Courses

Front End Developer Track, Udacity - One Million Arab Coders program

August 2018

Intro to programming nanodegree, Udacity

July 2018

Responsive Web Design, freecodecamp

July 2018

Personal Skills

Ability to work well under pressure.

Ability to learn new tasks quickly.

Can work individually and as an effective team member.

Very good in communication and presentation skills.

Details

Date / Place of birth 15/6/1992

Suez

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

Sass

JavaScript

jQuery

React

Redux

Languages

Arabic

English

Links

Portfolio

Github

Personal Data

Date of birth: 15/06/1992

Marital Status: single

Nationality: Egyptian

Military service: complete with a good idol

Mobile Phone: +201020285787

Portfolio: https://shadyagamy.github.io/ShAgamyPortfolio/